One Marriage. One Family. Under God.
Indivisible is a drama, war film directed by David G. Evans.
Upon returning from serving in the U.S.
Army, Chaplain Darren Turner faces a crisis that shatters his Family and Faith in God but
through the help of his fellow soldiers, he returns to his faith and family
Darren Turner, played by Justin Bruening.
Heather Turner, played by Sarah Drew.
Michael Lewis, played by Jason George.
Tonya Lewis, played by Tia Mowry.
Sgt. Shonda Peterson, played by Skye P. Marshall.
Lance Bradley, played by Tanner Stine.
Indivisible is a 2018 American Christian war drama film directed by David G.
Evans, who co-wrote the screenplay with Cheryl McKay Price and Peter White.
Starring Sarah Drew, Justin Bruening, Tia Mowry and Eric Close, the film is based on the true story of Darren
Turner, a United States Army chaplain who struggles to balance his faith and the Iraq War.
It was released in the United States on October 26, 2018 by Pure
Flix, and received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of army, faith, god, iraq war, chaplain.
The tone is emotional.